Finding Aid for the Dewey Daane Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Cassette Tapes- Part A:, 11/8/88 (Box 25)
  - Part A: 1, 11/16/88 (Box 25)
  - Part A: 2, 11/16/88 (Box 25)
  - International Finance: Part 1:, 11/2/88 (Box 25)
  - Part B: Side 1, 11/30/88 (Box 25)
  - International Finance: Side 1, 12/2/88 (Box 25)
  - Part A: Side 1, 11/30/88 (Box 25)
  - International Finance: Part 2:, 11/2/88 (Box 25)
- The New Economic Role of American States by R. Scott Fosler 1988 [2 copies] (Box 26)
- Economic Report of the President-, Jan 1976 (Box 26)
- Economic Report of the President-, Jan 1977 (Box 26)
- Economic Report of the President-, Jan 1980 (Box 26)
- Economic Report of the President-, Jan 1981 (Box 26)
- Economic Report of the President-, Feb 1982 (Box 26)
- Economic Report of the President-, Feb 1983 (Box 26)
- Economic Report of the President-, Feb 1984 (Box 26)
- Economic Report of the President-, Feb 1985 (Box 26)
- Economic Report of the President-, Feb 1986 (Box 26)
- Economic Report of the President-, Jan 1987 (Box 26)
- Economic Report of the President-, Feb 1988 (Box 26)
- Brookings Institute Annual Report, 1970 (Box 26)
- Brookings Paper on Economic Activity- 1970 No 2 (Box 26)
- Brookings Paper on Economic Activity- 1970 No 3 (Box 26)
- Brookings Paper on Economic Activity- 1971 No 1 (Box 26)
- Brookings Paper on Economic Activity- 1971 No 2 (Box 26)
- Brookings Paper on Economic Activity- 1971 No 3 (Box 26)
- Brookings Paper on Economic Activity- 1972 No 1 (Box 26)
- Brookings Paper on Economic Activity- 1972 No 2 (Box 26)
- Brookings Paper on Economic Activity- 1972 No 3 (Box 26)
- Brookings Paper on Economic Activity- 1973 No 1 (Box 26)
- Brookings Paper on Economic Activity- 1973 No 2 (Box 26)
- Brookings Paper on Economic Activity- 1973 No 3 (Box 26)
- Brookings Paper on Economic Activity- 1974 No 1 (Box 26)
- Brookings Paper on Economic Activity- 1974 No 2 (Box 26)
- Brookings Paper on Economic Activity- 1974 No 3 (Box 26)
- Brookings Paper on Economic Activity- 1975 No 1 (Box 26)
- Brookings Paper on Economic Activity- 1975 No 2 (Box 26)
- Brookings Paper on Economic Activity- 1975 No 3 [2 copies] (Box 26)
- Brookings Paper on Economic Activity- 1976 No 1 (Box 26)
- Brookings Paper on Economic Activity, 1976 No 2 (Box 26)
- Brookings Paper on Economic Activity, 1976 No 3 (Box 26)
- Brookings Paper on Economic Activity, 1977 No 1 (Box 26)
- Brookings Paper on Economic Activity, 1978 No 2 (Box 26)
- Brookings Paper on Economic Activity, 1978 No 3 (Box 26)
- Brookings Paper on Economic Activity, 1979 No 2 (Box 26)
- Brookings Paper on Economic Activity, 1981 No 2 (Box 26)
- Investing in America’s Future- CED [12 copies] (Box 27)
- Economic Report of the President, Jan 1956 (Box 27)
- Economic Report of the President, Jan 1957 (Box 27)
- Economic Report of the President, Jan 1958 (Box 27)
- Economic Report of the President-, Jan 1959 (Box 27)
- Economic Report of the President-, Jan 1960 (Box 27)
- Economic Report of the President-, Jan 1961 (Box 27)
- Economic Report of the President-, Jan 1962 (Box 27)
- Economic Report of the President-, Jan 1963 (Box 27)
- Economic Report of the President-, Jan 1964 (Box 27)
- Economic Report of the President-, Jan 1965 (Box 27)
- Economic Report of the President-, Jan 1966 (Box 27)
- Economic Report of the President-, Jan 1967 (Box 27)
- Economic Report of the President-, Feb 1968 (Box 27)
- Economic Report of the President-, Jan 1969 (Box 27)
- Economic Report of the President-, Feb 1970 (Box 27)
- Economic Report of the President-, Feb 1971 (Box 27)
- Economic Report of the President-, Jan 1972 (Box 27)
- Economic Report of the President-, Jan 1973 (Box 27)
- Economic Report of the President-, Feb 1974 (Box 27)
- Economic Report of the President-, Feb 1975 (Box 27)
- Economic Report of the President- Jan 1979 [2 copies] (Box 27)
- Treasury- Annual Report- Finance, 1950 (Box 28)
- Treasury- Annual Report- Finance, 1951 (Box 28)
- Treasury- Annual Report- Finance, 1954 (Box 28)
- Treasury- Annual Report- Finance, 1955 (Box 28)
- Treasury- Annual Report- Finance, 1956 (Box 28)
- Treasury- Annual Report- Finance, 1957 (Box 28)
- Treasury- Annual Report- Finance, 1958 (Box 28)
- Treasury- Annual Report- Finance, 1959 (Box 28)
- Treasury- Annual Report- Finance, 1960 (Box 28)
- Treasury- Annual Report- Finance, 1961 (Box 28)
- Treasury- Annual Report- Finance, 1962 (Box 28)
- Treasury- Annual Report- Finance, 1963 (Box 28)
- Treasury- Annual Report- Finance, 1964 (Box 28)
- Treasury- Annual Report- Finance, 1965 (Box 28)
- Treasury- Annual Report- Finance, 1966 (Box 28)
- Treasury- Annual Report- Finance, 1967 (Box 28)
- Treasury- Annual Report- Statistical Appendix, 1968 (Box 28)
- Treasury- Annual Report- Finance, 1969 (Box 28)
- IMF Annual Report-, 1964 (Box 29)
- IMF Annual Report-, 1966 (Box 29)
- IMF Annual Report-, 1967 (Box 29)
- IMF Annual Report-, 1968 (Box 29)
- IMF Annual Report-, 1969 (Box 29)
- IMF Annual Report-, 1970 (Box 29)
- IMF Annual Report-, 1971 (Box 29)
- IMF Annual Report-, 1972 (Box 29)
- IMF Annual Report-, 1973 (Box 29)
- IMF Annual Report-, 1974 (Box 29)
- IMF Annual Report-, 1975 (Box 29)
- IMF Annual Report-, 1976 (Box 29)
- IMF Annual Report-, 1977 (Box 29)
- IMF Annual Report-, 1978 (Box 29)
- IMF Annual Report-, 1979 (Box 29)
- International Centre for Settlement of Investment Disputes 4th Annual Report, 1969-70 (Box 29)
- BIS- A Collection of Central Bankers’ Speeches, (1964-1965) Mar 1966 (Box 30)
- BIS- A Collection of Central Bankers’ Speeches, (1966-1967) Mar 1968 (Box 30)
- BIS- A Collection of Central Bankers’ Speeches, (1968-1969) Mar 1970 (Box 30)
- BIS- A Collection of Central Bankers’ Speeches, (1972-1973) Mar 1974 (Box 30)
- BIS Annual Report, 1961/62 (Box 30)
- BIS Annual Report, 1962/63 (Box 30)
- BIS Annual Report, 1963/64 (Box 30)
- BIS Annual Report, 1964/65 (Box 30)
- BIS Annual Report, 1965/66 (Box 30)
- BIS Annual Report, 1966/67 (Box 30)
- BIS Annual Report, 1967/68 (Box 30)
- BIS Annual Report, 1968/69 (Box 30)
- BIS Annual Report, 1969/70 (Box 30)
- BIS Annual Report, 1970/71 (Box 30)
- BIS Annual Report, 1971/72 (Box 30)
- BIS Annual Report, 1972/73 (Box 30)
- BIS Annual Report, 1974/75 (Box 30)
- BIS Annual Report, 1975/76 (Box 30)
- BIS Annual Report, 1976/77 (Box 30)
- BIS Annual Report, 1977/78 (Box 30)
- BIS Annual Report, 1978/79 (Box 30)
- BIS Annual Report, 1979/80 (Box 31)
- BIS Annual Report, 1980/81 (Box 31)
- BIS Annual Report, 1981/82 (Box 31)
- BIS Annual Report, 1982/83 (Box 31)
- BIS Annual Report, 1983/84 (Box 31)
- BIS Annual Report, 1984/85 (Box 31)
- BIS Annual Report, 1985/86 (Box 31)
- BIS Annual Report, 1986/87 (Box 31)
- BIS Annual Report, 1987/88 (Box 31)
- CED- Strengthening the World Monetary System, July 1973 (Box 31)
- NFTC- Declaration of the 59th National Foreign Trade Convention (Box 31)
- IMF- International Currency Review Vol. 12 No 4 (Box 31)
- IMF- International Currency Review Vol. 13 No 4 (Box 31)
- International Monetary Advisory Board- Supply-side Economics, World Finance and the IMF Aug 24-25, 1980 NYMonetary Policy Report for (Box 31)
- Gottfried Haberler- The U.S. Balance of Payments: Freedom of Controls (Box 31)
- Federal Reserve System- Staff Economic Studies- International Money Markets and Flexible Exchange Rates Stanley W. Black (Box 31)
- Federal Reserve System- Staff Economic Studies- Explaining Changes in Euro-dollar Positions in study of Banks in 4 Euro Countries by Rodney H. Mills, Jr. (Box 31)
- CED- Gold, the Dollar and the World Monetary System, Jun 1965 (Box 31)
- The Atlantic Council- Sep 18, 1972- Interim Report (Box 31)
- International Chamber of Commerce- Development in International Monetary Policy, Feb 15, 1967 (Box 31)
- A Debate on the Eurodollar Market (Box 31)
- Overseas Development Council- Occasional Paper No 6- Special Rights and Development Aid by Geoffrey W. Maynard (Box 31)
- Executive Branch Gatt Studies- Senate Finance Committee, Mar 1974 (Box 31)
- Princeton University- Essay in International Finance- No 150 Dec 1982- The Inefficacy of Trade Policy by Robert E. Baldwin (Box 31)
- American Bankers Association- U.S. Gold Policy (Box 31)
- Some Basic Facts about Reserve Currencies and Gold by J.P. Koszul (Box 31)
- A Proposed Solution for the Dollar Overhang Problem- David L. Grove, 1972 (Box 31)
- The Japanese Financial System in Comparative Perspective- Joint Economic Committee Congress, Mar 12, 1982 (Box 31)
- AEI- The Dollar-Mark-Yen Crisis, 1973 Gottfried Haberler (Box 31)
- CED- May 1961 The International Position of the Dollar (Box 31)
- Finance and Development Quarterly No 2 1969- 25 Years Since Bretton Woods (Box 31)
- The American Economic Review- Vol. 62 No 4, Sep 1972 (Box 31)
- The Atlantic Council of the U.S. Policy Papers- Summit Meetings and Collective Leadership in the, 1980’s (Box 31)
- CED- The U.S. and the European Community: Policies for a Changing World Economy-, Nov 1971 (Box 31)
- Tokyo Round (Box 31)
- European Review- Winter, 1970-71 (Box 31)
- Feshbach Conference Call-, 9/5/91 (Box 32)
- Feshbach-, Oct 18, 1991 (Box 32)
- Feshbach Conference Call, 8/29/91 (Box 32)
- Feshbach Conference Call, 8/29/91 (Box 32)
- Feshbach Conference Call, 8/15/91 (Box 32)
- Feshbach-, Aug 8, 1991 (Box 32)
- Consultant- Feshbach Brothers (Box 32)
- Feshbach Conference Call, 6/13/91 (Box 32)
- Feshbach Conference Call, 6/20/91 (Box 32)
- Feshbach Conference, 6/6/91 (Box 32)
- Feshbach Conference Call, 5/23/91 (Box 32)
- Other Reference Material (Box 32)
- Feshbach Conference, May 16, 1991 (Box 32)
- Feshbach Conference, 5/6/91 (Box 32)
- Feshbach Conference Call, 4/25/91 (Box 32)
- Feshbach Conference Call, 4/18/91 (Box 32)
- Feshbach Conference Call, 4/12/91 (Box 32)
- Feshbach Conference Call, 4/4/91 (Box 32)
- Feshbach Conference Call, 3/28/91 (Box 32)
- Boston… America’s Home Port; a Sketch book by Jack Frost (Box 32)
- Business International Executive Services- Operating in a Floating Exchange Rate World and Cash Management (Box 32)
- Federal Reserve Bank of Chicago- Staff Memoranda- Financial Services in Transition: The Effects of Non-Bank Competitors- Rosenblum and Pavel (Box 32)
- Federal Home loan Bank Board- Thrift- Institution Failures: Causes and Policy Issues by Barth, Brumbaugh, Sauerhaft and Wang (Box 32)
- Conference on Bank Structure and Competition- May 2-3, 1985 Yes-Private Sector Depositor Protection in a Viable Alternative to Federal Deposit Insurance by Bert Ely, 1985 (Box 32)
- Binder- Federal Reserve Bank of Chicago- May 2-3, 1985- Conference on Bank Structure and Competition (Box 32)
- Binder- The Management of Foreign Policy: Success and Failure in Kennedy’s Collegial Approach by Thomas T. Earthman, June 1975 (Box 32)
- Louis Camu 1905-1976- Booklet (Box 32)
- 2 Pamphlets on France (Box 32)
- Annual Report of the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation, 1958 (Box 33)
- Annual Report of the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation, 1959 (Box 33)
- Annual Report of the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation, 1960 (Box 33)
- Annual Report of the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation, 1961 (Box 33)
- Annual Report of the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation, 1962 (Box 33)
- Annual Report of the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation, 1963 (Box 33)
- Annual Report of the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation, 1964 (Box 33)
- Annual Report of the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation, 1965 (Box 33)
- Annual Report of the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation, 1966 (Box 33)
- Annual Report of the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation, 1967 (Box 33)
- Annual Report of the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation, 1968 (Box 33)
- Annual Report of the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation, 1969 (Box 33)
- Annual Report of the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation, 1970 (Box 33)
- Annual Report of the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation, 1971 (Box 33)
- Annual Report of the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation, 1972 (Box 33)
- Treasury- Annual Report- Finance-, 1946 (Box 33)
- Treasury- Annual Report- Finance-, 1947 (Box 33)
- Treasury- Annual Report- Finance-, 1948 (Box 33)
- Treasury- Annual Report- Finance-, 1949 (Box 33)
- Treasury- Annual Report- Finance-, 1952 (Box 33)
- Treasury- Annual Report- Finance-, 1953 (Box 33)
- Treasury- Annual Report- Finance-, 1970 (Box 33)
- Treasury- Annual Report- Finance-, 1971 (Box 33)
- Treasury- Annual Report- Finance-, 1972 (Box 33)
- Treasury- Annual Report- Statistical Appendix-, 1969 (Box 33)
- Treasury- Annual Report- Statistical Appendix- 1970 [2 copies] (Box 33)
- Treasury- Annual Report- Statistical Appendix-, 1971 (Box 33)
- Treasury- Annual Report- Statistical Appendix-, 1972 (Box 33)
- Treasury- Annual Report- Statistical Appendix-, 1973 (Box 33)
- Department of the Treasury- Tax Plan Materials-, 1981 (Box 34)
- Department of the Treasury- Public Policy for American Capital Markets, 1974 (Box 34)
- Department of the Treasury- Recommendations for Change in the U.S. Financial System, Aug 3, 1973 (Box 34)
- Joint Treasury- Federal Reserve Study of the U.S. Government Securities Market- Staff Studies- Part 1 (Box 34)
- Joint Treasury- Federal Reserve Study of the U.S. Government Securities Market- Staff Studies- Part 2 (Box 34)
- Joint Treasury- Federal Reserve Study of the U.S. Government Securities Market- Joint Statement, July 24, 1959 (Box 34)
- Joint Treasury- Federal Reserve Study of the U.S. Government Securities Market- Staff Studies- Part III (Box 34)
- Treasury- Federal Reserve Study of the Government Securities Market- Part 1, July 27, 1959 (Box 34)
- Treasury- Federal Reserve Study of the Government Securities Market- Part 2 Factual Review for, 1958 (Box 34)
- Treasury- Federal Reserve Study of the Government Securities Market- Part 3 Supplementary Studies (Box 34)
- Improvements needed in the Federal Reserve Reporting System for Recognized Dealers in Governmental Securities-, Oct 6, 1971 (Box 34)
- Treasury Papers-, July 1975- Dec 1975, Jan 1976- May 1976, July 1976- Dec 1976 (Box 34)
- The U.S.- Budget in Brief FY, 1985 (Box 34)
- Federal Funds Market- Origin and Development, Parker B. Willis FRB of Boston (Box 34)
- Congress and the Federal Budget- Tax Foundation Inc. – Govt. Finance Brief No 23 (Box 34)
- 2nd Monetary Policy Report for 1980- Senate Committee (Box 34)
- Banking Secrecy in Switzerland (Box 34)
- Federal Trust Funds: Budgetary and Other Implications- Tax Foundation Inc. (Box 34)
- The U.S. Budget in Brief FY, 1981 (Box 34)
- 2nd Concurrent Resolution on the Budget FY, 1981 (Box 34)
- Bank Liquidity Re-examined- Trustees of the Banking Research Fund Association of Reserve City Bankers (Box 34)
- FRB of Kansas City- Economic Review, Apr 1980 (Box 34)
- Federal Reserve Policy- Making and Its Problems- FRB of Atlanta (Box 34)
- FRB of NY- Research Paper- Is Short Run Monetary Control Feasible? by John Ciccolo (Box 34)
- FRB of Atlanta- Jun 1977 Working Paper Series- Regional Impacts of Monetary and Fiscal Policies in the Postwar Period” Some Initial Tests- William D. Toal (Box 34)
- FRB of NY- Research Paper- Floating Jointly: The Mechanics of the European Community’s Currency Arrangements- Martin Barrett (Box 34)
- FRB of NY- Research Paper- The Reconstruction of the International Monetary System: The Attempts of 1922 and 1933- Stephen V. O. Clarke (Box 34)
- FRB of NY- Research Paper- Reserve Requirements Abroad- George Garvy (Box 34)
- FRB of NY- Research Paper- Foreign Banks in the U.S.: Scope and Growth of Operations- Fred H. Klopstock (Box 34)
- FRB of NY- Research Paper- Comments on Demand and Supply Functions for Stocks of Eurodollar deposits: an Empirical Study by Ann-Marie Meulendyke (Box 34)
- FRB of NY- Research Paper- Impact of Excess Reserves on the Relationship Between RPD and MI by Ann-Marie Meulendyke (Box 34)
- FRB of NY- Research Paper- Rising Interest Rates and Cost Push Inflation- Stephen A. Seelig (Box 34)
- FRB of NY- Research Paper- Implementing Open Market Policy with Monetary Aggregate Objectives- Richard G. Davis (Box 34)
- 26- Public Policy Issues in U.S. Banking Abroad- Robert C. Holand, Apr 8, 1975 (Box 34)
- 258- The Role of Banks in the Intl Financial System- Nancy H. Teeters, Jun 14, 1983 (Box 34)
- 263- Statement by Michael Bradfield, July 21, 1983 (Box 34)
- 312- Statement by William Taylor May 15, 1985 (Box 34)
- 316 The Transition to Interstate Banking; Remarks by Martha R. Seger, Jan 8, 1985 (Box 34)
- 324- Statement by William Taylor, Sep 11, 1985 (Box 34)
- 331- Farm Financial Experience and Agricultural Banking Exchange- Statement by Emmanuel Melichar, Oct 23, 1985 (Box 34)
- 340- Statement by Frederick R. Dahl, Mar 4, 1986 (Box 34)
- 345- Statement by William Taylor, Apr 9, 1986 (Box 34)
- 347- Statement by Frederick R. Dahl, Apr 22, 1986 (Box 34)
- 348- Remarks by Wayne D. Angell, Apr 22, 1986 (Box 34)
- 349- Remarks by Manuel H. Johnson, Apr 26, 1986 (Box 34)
- The Role of Money in Achieving Economic Growth and Price Stability- Beryl W. Sprinkel (Box 34)
- The Monetary Interpretation of History- James Tobin (Box 34)
- “Supply-side Effects of Fiscal Policy: Some Preliminary Hypotheses” Robert E. Keleher, Jan 18, 1979 (Box 34)
- A Time of Change for Financial Institutions by Francis H. Schott, Feb 1982 (Box 34)
- Monetary Targets- Their Contributions to Policy Formation by Lawrence K. Roos, May 10, 1979 (Box 34)
- New England Economic Review- Jul/ Aug 1976- The Forecasting Performance in the Early 1970’s- Stephen K. McNees (Box 34)
- The Dimensions of the Economic and Financial No Man’s Land- Henry Kaufman, Jul 23, 1979 (Box 34)
- The Difference Factors: Their Influence on American Credit Markets-, Oct 23, 1979 (Box 34)
- The International Financial System and Capital Shortages- Mar 31, 1976- Geoffrey Ball (Box 34)
- BIS- 51st Annual General Meeting Jun 15, 1981- Speech by J. Zijlstra (Box 34)
- U.S. Foreign Economic Strategy as seen in “ Classified” Documents by Hiroshi Ando-, Aug 9, 1981 (Box 34)
- Reflections on the Monetary Crisis: Diagnosis and Therapies- Max Ikle-, Nov 1971 (Box 34)
- The Reform of the International Payment System- Franco Modigliani (Box 34)
- Convertibility and Consolation: A Survey of Options for Future Reform and The System- Peter B. Keehn, Dec 29, 1972 (Box 34)
- Tripartite Report on Reshaping the International Economic Order, Dec 21, 1971 (Box 34)
- The Case for the Par-Value System, 1971- Samuel I. Katz (Box 34)
- International Commercial Banks-A Link between Two Systems- C. M. van Vlierden (Box 34)
- A Proposed Reform of the International Monetary System- C. Fred Bergsten (Box 34)
- Statement by C. Fred Bergsten-, Jun 23, 1971 (Box 34)
- The Use of SDR Finance for Collectively Agreed Purposes by Robert Triffin (Box 34)
- The Journal of Commercial Bank Lending-, Nov 1970 (Box 34)
- Reprint from Banking- Journal of ABA- Jan 1974 and Apr 1974, Letter to Editor and Response from Editor (Box 34)
- Irving Trust Co.- The Economic View from One Wall Street (Box 34)
- Blyth Eastman Dillon Investment Research- The Adequacy of Structure of Capital for Bankers and Bank (Box 34)
- Holding Companies- William M. Weiant and William A. Wood III (Box 34)
- Regulation and Control of the United Kingdom Banking and Financial Structure- J.S.G. Wilson, 1969 (Box 34)
- Inflation and Corporate Profits- Beorge Terborgh (Box 34)
- Money and Output: Keynes and Friedman in Historical Perspective- J.H. Wood (Box 34)
- Corporate Capital Structures and Financing Patterns:, 1977-1980 (Box 34)
- Social Science Quarterly- Dec 1973 The Economic Affiliations of Directors of Federal Reserve District Banks- Thomas Harrilesky, William P. Yohe, David Schirm (Box 34)
- Economic Notes- Vol. III No 2, May/Aug 1974 (Box 34)
- AEI- Cause for Moderation in the Economic Recovery of 1971- William Fellner (Box 34)
- The Term Structure of Interest Rates- W. Braddock Hickman (Box 34)
- Second World Banking Conference Dec 10-11, 1975 (Box 34)
- Recommendations Regarding Foreign Access to the U.S. Securities Market-, Jul 1973 (Box 34)
- Trade Policy for the Seventies- Lawrence B. Krause, 1971 (Box 34)
- Vision- The European Business Magazine- Feb 15, 1973 No 27 (Box 34)
- The 2nd Amendment of the Fund’s Articles of Agreement- Joseph Gold, 1978 (Box 34)
- Euromoney-, Sep 1972 (Box 34)
- European Direct Investments in the U.S.- H.E. Ekblom- Harvard Business Review, Jul/Aug 1973 (Box 34)
- International Business Week, Sep 21, 1981 (Box 34)
- Statements of the U.S. Treasury Concerning the Devaluation of the French Franc, Aug 8, 1969 (Box 34)
- Journal of Finance- Vol. 19 No 3 Sep 1964- The Implications of Triangular Arbitrage for Forward Exchange Policy – Henry N. Goldstein (Box 34)
- The U.S. Balance of Payments Problem: Recent Developments and Prospects, Feb 5, 1973 (Box 34)
- U.S. Liquid Funds Abroad, The Eurodollar Market and Foreign Commercial Bank Balances in the U.S.-, Jun 29, 1965 (Box 34)
- Reference A- Jan 28, 1971- Scenario III- Exchange Rate Realignment and Related Materials (Box 34)
- Reference B- May 8, 1971- Contingency (Box 34)
- Carter H. Golembe Associates, Inc.- Hunt Commission Report: The Second Time Around Vol., 1973-7 (Box 34)
- Folder- FRB of Boston- Bald Peak Conference, 10/12-14/87 (Box 34)
- Folder- FRB of Boston- Bald Peak Conference, 10/6-8/82 (Box 34)
- Tennessean- Wed., June 3, 1987 (Box 35)
- Nashville Banner- Wed. June 3, 1987 2nd Edition (Box 35)
- Nashville Banner- Wed. June 3, 1987 Final Edition (Box 35)
- Nashville Banner- Mon. June 15, 1987 1st Edition (Box 35)
- Nashville Banner- Mon. June 15, 1987 2nd Edition (Box 35)
- Nashville Banner- Tues. December 8, 1987 Final Edition (Box 35)
- Nashville Banner- Thurs. April 13, 1989 1st Edition (Box 35)
- Tennessean Fri., April 14, 1989 (Box 35)
- Nashville Banner- Fri. April 14, 1989 (clipping) (Box 35)
- Nashville Banner- Tues. April 18, 1989 1st Edition (Box 35)
- Nashville Banner- Mon. June 12, 1989 1st Edition (Box 35)
- VU Register-, April 21, 1989 (Box 35)
- The Owen Manager- Vol. 9 No 2 Spring 1988- 2 Copies and 2 Photocopies (Box 35)
- Old Kent State Bank- Michigan Account- Bank Statements (Box 35)
  - and Misc., Jan 1987- Oct 1987, Dec 1987- Sep 1989, Nov 1989- Feb 1990, Apr 1990- May 1990 (Box 35)
- Bank Books- (Box 35)
  - JDD- Travel Account- Check Stubs and Checks--, 9/84- 1/89 (Box 35)
  - JDD- American Securities Bank (D.C.) Check Stubs 251-400 --, 10/80-5/88 (Box 35)
  - JDD- Commerce Union Bank Deposit Slip Book—, 1/86-1/89 (Box 35)
  - JDD- Sovran Bank -Check Stubs 757-1008 and Deposit Stubs 1075-1099, 6/88-11/88 (Box 35)
  - JDD- Sovran Bank -Check Stubs 1009-1260 and Deposit Stubs 1270-1290, 11/88-3/89 (Box 35)
  - JDD- Sovran Bank -Check Stubs 1261-1512 and Unnumbered Deposit Stubs, 3/89-8/89 (Box 35)
  - JDD- Sovran Bank -Check Stubs 1513-1765 and Unnumbered Deposit Stubs, 8/89-1/90 (Box 35)
- JDD- Sovran Account Statements and Cancelled Checks-, Jan-Dec 1988 (Box 35)
- JDD- Sovran Travel Account Statements and Cancelled Checks-, Apr-Dec 1988 (Box 35)
- JDD- Washington Account Statements, Aug-Dec 1988 (Box 35)
- JDD- Sovran Account Statements and Cancelled Checks-, Jan-Dec 1989 (Box 35)
- JDD- Sovran Travel Account Statements and Cancelled Checks-, Jan-Dec 1989 (Box 35)
- JDD- Sovran Travel Account Deposit Slips (Box 35)
- JDD- Washington Account Statements, Jan-Dec 1989 (Box 35)
- Blue Chip Deposit Slips (Box 35)
- Vandy Paystubs, 8/89 and 9/89 (Box 35)
- JDD- Sovran Account Statements and Cancelled Checks-, Jan-May 1990 (Box 35)
- JDD- Sovran Travel Account Statements and Cancelled Checks-, Jan-Jun 1990 (Box 35)
- JDD- Washington Account Statements, Feb-Jun 1990 (Box 35)
- American Economic Review (Box 36)
  - Dec 1968 (Box 36)
  - Mar 1969, Jun 1969, Sep 1969, Sep Supplement 1969, Dec 1969 Mar 1970 (Box 36)
  - Mar 1971 (Box 36)
  - Dec 1973 (Box 36)
  - Dec 1974 (Box 36)
  - Mar 1975, Jun 1975, Sep 1975, Dec 1975 (Box 36)
  - Mar 1976, Jun 1976, Sep 1976, Dec 1976 (Box 36)
  - Mar 1977, Jun 1977, Sep 1977 (Box 36)